[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":32997,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":558310,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":10562,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":568873,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1884,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":570761,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5 "],"rt":3038,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":573800,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1181,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":574991,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3585,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":578576,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1287,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":579863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1920,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":581783,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":999,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":582782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum i s 6 or b igger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4067,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":586849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1033,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":587892,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2304,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":590196,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":871,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":591067,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2052,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":593119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":957,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":594076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to  perform  +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2803,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":596879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1093,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":597972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2863,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":600835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":892,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":601727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1798,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":603526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":889,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":604415,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":7328,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":611744,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similar ly, 3 is  its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":21064,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":632810,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3533,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":636343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4480,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":640823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an e lement i s the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2053,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":642886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":920,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":643806,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1793,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":645599,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"C orrect!  The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":788,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":646397,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1795,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":648192,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":829,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":649021,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br />  (Rememb er, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["5","6"],"rt":3541,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":652563,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":12282,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":664845,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes ","response_history":["yes"],"rt":10299,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":675144,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":13400,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":688544,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub>  1. Beca use of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":18774,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":707318,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5054,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":712373,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1523,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":713896,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2577,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":716473,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":17613,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":734086,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2797,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":736885,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":3200,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":740085,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2377,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":742463,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":2179,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":744642,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":28181,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":772823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":7112,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":779936,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3706,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":783644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 b ecause 5  + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1141,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":784785,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["5","6"],"rt":4136,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":788921,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2437,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":791358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":795358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2248,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":797607,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2002,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":799610,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5 because don't subtract 9","response_history":["4","5 because don't subtract 9"],"rt":13780,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":813390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in word s how yo u got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 because 12-9","response_history":["3 because 12-3","3 because 12-9"],"rt":8573,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":821963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"Whatever ends up as 0","response_history":["Whatever ends up as 0"],"rt":18796,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":840759,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["3","4"],"rt":4260,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":845029,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What  is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2390,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":847419,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because 3+6-9=0","response_history":["6 because 3+6-9=0"],"rt":16666,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":864085,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes you can generate all numbers with 2","response_history":["No","N","Yes you can generate all numbers with 2"],"rt":54047,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":918142,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes you can generate all numbers with 3","response_history":["Yes you can generate all numbers with 3"],"rt":34359,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":952501,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes you can generate all numbers with 5","response_history":["Yes you can generate all nunmbe","Yes you can generate all nunmb","Yes you can generate all nunm","Yes you can generate all nun","Yes you can generate all numbers with 5"],"rt":25393,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":977904,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes you can generate all numbers with 6","response_history":["Yes you can generate all numbers with 5","Yes you can generate all numbers with 6"],"rt":27129,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1005034,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":4445,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1009486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Wh at is th e formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1","response_history":["n-1"],"rt":45241,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1054727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n-x","response_history":["x-1","x-","x","n-x"],"rt":13479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1068206,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know","response_history":["I  don't know"],"rt":15656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1083872,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1088592,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":2997,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1091589,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4102,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1095691,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I don't even understand the question","response_history":["I don't even understand the question"],"rt":35698,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1131389,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["So metimes","Always"],"rt":12338,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1143727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"No one knows what you're talking about","response_history":["You think anyo","0$","0#","0% of ","No one n","No one knows what you're talking about"],"rt":24405,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1168132,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":5691,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1173823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1318,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1175144,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"32","response_history":["32"],"rt":1439,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1176584,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelo rs Degre e","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2230,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1178814,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Pre-calculus","response_history":["Pre-calculus ","Pre-calculus"],"rt":9831,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1188655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 -  never heard of it"],"rt":3393,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1192050,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":2127,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1194177,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":3227,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1197404,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2269,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1199673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2164,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1201837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1753,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1203590,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4912,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1208502,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2931,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1211436,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":3250,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1214686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]